that beverages containing added sugar might be harmful.
In the study, researchers analyzed information from over 80,000 women and 37,000
men. that beverages containing added sugar might be harmful.
men. Participants worked in the health profession.
They were followed for approximately three decades.
They completed surveys about their diet every four years.
Participants worked in the health profession.
They were followed for approximately three decades.
They completed surveys about their diet every four years.
Participants worked in the health profession.
They were followed for approximately three decades.
They completed surveys about their diet every four years.
They also answered questions about sleep and exercise and health every two years.
The more beverages containing added sugar that people drank, the greater their risk
of death was during the study period.
of was during the study period.
These beverages included soda, energy drinks, and sports drinks.
beverages included soda, energy drinks, sports drinks.
These included soda, drinks.
beverages energy The added sugar were not part of the study.
These beverages included soda, energy drinks, sports drinks.
These Beverages like pure fruit juice which are sweet but do not contain added